[{"answer": "Well, it is interesting, Piers, just how difficult information has been to get.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Do you have any way of knowing?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think that we have to deal with the scientific facts here.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Do you feel in danger where you are now?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "It's desperate but Sanjay is correct, it's confused.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Clearly a pretty desperate situation, isn't it?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, the building has been blown away the secondary containment on a couple of these places so you could in theory drop water in.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "And Matthew, finally and very quickly, is the situation worse tonight than it was last night?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "There have been reports that Saudi forces have been involved.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "What do you know about that?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Yes, it's a catastrophe and she says it's minute by minute.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "And Wolf, what did she have to say about the ongoing crisis at the Fukushima nuclear plant in Japan, because it seems to be getting ever more dangerous?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "It's a good question because her job approval numbers in our latest CNN -- CNN poll, she's -- two-thirds of the American public give her favorable ratings.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "What's behind it, do you think?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, I really only know what we've put out on our Web site, Piers, and obviously, you know, I'm extremely worried for my four colleagues.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Do you have any latest news on that?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "RIEDMAN: No, I really can't.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Can you quite believe what you're witnessing here?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, the common thread is the aspiration of Arabs of all ages to want to run their own lives in a world where they can increasingly see how other people are living and see just how fracture behind they are.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "When you talk about the dominos, are they very different kinds of dominos we're seeing here or do you detect a common thread?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "You know, I don't want to make any predictions that the whole Saudi regime is going to fall but this is what I think is important to keep in mind, Piers.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Do you think there's any danger the House of Saud could fall?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "You know, I think it's very understandable, Piers, that they would feel exactly the mixed emotions that you're describing.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Is this opportunity or could this go horribly wrong for them?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think he'd talk to me, but good luck.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "If you were sitting down, as I am, with Prime Minister Netanyahu tomorrow, what would you ask him?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, there's two things I would say.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Is that the prudent course of action?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Piers, let's take Egypt first.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "You can hardly blame him for wanting to see how things play out, can you?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "There's no question that any prime minister would have to speak first in the tones of grief and even anger about a horrific murder that we saw in the area.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "If you're Benjamin Netanyahu, what do you say to your people, not just about that incident, in terms of an appropriate response, but also in terms of this cargo ship which was seized apparently carrying a load of weapons to Gaza?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Well, of course, like everyone, I'm shocked by what happened and I feel terrible for the Japanese people.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Rudy, what do you make of these appalling scenes in Japan?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "You know, I can't say because I'm not there.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "In terms of how they have dealt with this disaster so far, do you think they've been doing the right things?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "No, because I know them well.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Have you been as stunned as the rest of us by the way they have handled this?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Prime Minister Netanyahu is a remarkable man.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "But there's a much bigger picture at play now, isn't there?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Piers, from the outside, right now, it looks like Gadhafi every day is solidifying his position.", "docId": "110316pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "How damaging would it be should Gadhafi win his battle, having murdered tens of thousands of his people by the time this finishes?", "qSentId": 462}]